先生，正在退出時間結 我們還活著
- Exiting the time knot now, sir. - We're alive !
我們成功了，長官，我們成功了
We made it, Commander. We made it.
上帝保佑，我們還活著
By Grabthar's hammer, we live to tell the tale.
系統正在調校功能
[ Computerized Voice ] Systems registering functional.
所有系統正常，長官
All systems are working, Commander.
我一點也不喜歡，太容易了
I don't like it. It was too easy.
哦，不，等等，到處都是時間結
- [ Boy ] Wait ! Oh, no. They're everywhere ! - [ Alarm Blaring ]
到處都是打開的時間結，這是個陷阱！！
- There are time knots opening everywhere ! - A trap !
我們被包圍了，長官
We're surrounded, Commander.
啊，天哪
- Aah ! - Ooh !
我們完了，先生，我們阻止不了
It's a core meltdown, sir. It can't be stopped.
投降也許是最好的選擇
Surrender may be our only option.
不！永不放棄！
No ! Never give up !
決不妥協！
Never surrender !
下命令吧，先生
Your orders, sir ?
先生？給大家下命令吧？
Sir ? Group orders ?
啟動 歐米茄13
Activate the Omega 13.
那麼？
- [ Audience Applauding ] - [ Man ] Well ?
嗯？好了，已經啟動了
Huh ? Well, there you are.
好！
- Yeah ! Huh ? - [ Audience Cheering, Applauding ]
好！我說的就是這個
Yeah ! Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
你們是第一個見到 久違了的《銀河探險》的人
You are the first people to see the lost Galaxy Quest--
第92集二章
episode 92 two-parter--
上次1982年的播出這集到現在已經20年了
since it was originally aired in 1982 !
哦，是的
- Huh ? Yeah ! All right. - [ Audience Applauding ]
現在，你們等待的時刻到了
And now, the moment you've all been waiting for--
勇敢無畏的NSEA保護者的全體人員
the intrepid crew of the N.S.E.A. Protector !
好啊，好啊
- Yeah ! Yeah ! - [ Crowd Cheering ]
紅頭巾，黑鞋子，等一下
[ Man ] Red scarf, black shoes. Wait.
白頭巾，黑鈕扣，白鞋子
White scarf, black buttons, white shoes.
夥計，他到底在哪裡？ 已經遲了一個半小時了
Man, where in the hell is he ? An hour and a half late ?
一個半小時了，真奇怪
- An hour and a half. - I mean, this is unreal.
他們已經等不及了
They're gonna start eating each other out there.
你聽到沒有？他撇下我們一個人 趕另外一個場子了
Oh, did you hear ? He booked another appearance without us.
你在開玩笑
You're kidding.
哦，嗯
Oh. Uh-- Um--
我怎麼會這樣？ 再也不會了
- How did I come to this ? - Not again.
我扮演曾經理查德三世，謝幕了5次
- I played Richard the Third. - Five curtain calls.
謝幕了5次啊，我曾是個真正的演員 看看我現在成了什麼樣子了
There were five curtain calls. I was an actor once, damn it ! Now look at me. Look at me !
我不能上台
I cannot go out there, and I won't say...
我再也不想說那些愚蠢的台詞了
that stupid line one more time !
我不能，我也不想 好吧，阿力克斯
- I can't, I won't. - Well, Alex, at least you had a part.
起碼觀眾喜歡你的角色
Okay ? You had a character people loved.
我是說，電視評論整整六段都是
I mean, my TV Guide interview was six paragraphs...
在說我的身材 和我的衣服多麼合身
about my boobs and how they fit into my suit.
根本沒有人關心我在演什麼
No one even bothered to ask me what I do on the show.
我們……等等 讓我想一想
You had the-- Wait. Wait, I'll think of it.
我再重複計算機的話 弗來德，哇喔!
- I repeated the computer, Fred. - Whew !
你們的指揮官來了！ 哈，哈！
Your commander is on deck ! Ha, ha !
今天霧很大，是嗎？
Wow, that smog is thick today, huh ?
我是不是太遲了 亞力克斯已經受不了了
- Am I too late for Alexander's panic attack ? - [ Objects Clattering ]
我沒有受不了，你應該看一看
Apparently not. You know, you should get that looked at.
是
[ Chuckles ] Yeah.
讓我們多看幾段
[ Emcee in Distance ] Let's take a look at a few more clips.
好的，我幹什麼呢？
Okay. What did I do ? Hmm ?
我們要見船員！ 什麼？
- [ Audience Chanting ] We want the crew ! - What ?
我們要見船員！ 整整4年，我們對這些船員 產生了很深的感情
- [ Chanting ] We want the crew ! - For those four seasons, we developed the same affection...
而船員們也有同樣的感情
for the crew as the crew had for each other.
他們不僅僅是探索太空的冒險家
These weren't just adventurers exploring space.
朋友 他們是朋友
- Friends. - These were friends.
不可思議 夠了，夥計
- Unbelievable. - You are so full of it, man !
沒什麼了不起的 那些傢伙在牆角放了一些佈景
It's not a big deal ! These guys put a little set in their basement.
我在那兒一個多小時 沒什麼的，格溫
I'm there about an hour. It's nothing, Gwen.
他們要見指揮官
They wanted the Commander.
他來了 亞歷山大，等一會。抓住他！抓住他！
- There he goes. - Alexander, wait a minute. Grab him ! Grab him !
我們要見他們，我們要見他們！ 好的！
- We want the crew ! We want the crew ! - [ Emcee ] Okay !
他們來了
Yeah ! Here we go !
來啊，老朋友
Come on, old friend. Old friend.
你搶了我的戲，我已經整整兩集沒出場了
You stole all my best lines. You cut me out of episode two entirely.
對不起。 桃麗麥迪遜，我最喜歡她了
- Excuse me. - [ Emcee ] Tawny Madison-- my personal favorite--
格溫迪馬克
- Gwen DeMarco ! - [ Crowd Cheering ]
好啊!
Yeah !
是，那正是我要說的，我們歡迎
Yeah, that's what I'm talkin' about ! Let's hear a warm welcome...
神槍手，拉多湯米韋伯
for crack gunner Laredo-- Tommy Webber !
你會上去的 我不
- You will go out there ! - I won't,
你說什麼都沒用
and nothing you say will make me.
戲必須演下去 弗來迪科溫！
- The show must go on. - [ Emcee ] Freddie Kwan !
媽的
- Damn you. - [ Emcee Continues, Indistinct ]
他媽的，我再也不會說 那些愚蠢的台詞了
Damn you. I won't say that stupid line one more time.
亞歷山大鄧恩
Tev'Meck-- Alexander Dane !
好啊
Yeah ! All right !
[ Crowd Cheering ]
上帝做證，我會為你報仇的！
By Grabthar's hammer, you shall be avenged !
是，好的
Yeah ! All right !
那傢伙真會演戲 最後
That guy can act. And finally,
我親愛的探險者迷們
my-- my fellow Questerians,
勇敢的NSEA保護者的指揮官
the brave Commander of the N.S.E.A. Protector,
彼得……彼得……彼得……
Peter, Peter, Peter, Peter, Peter,
昆西……昆西……昆西……
Quincy, Quincy, Quincy, Quincy, Taggart, Taggart, Taggart Taggart--
賈森耐斯密斯
- Jason Nesmith ! Yes ! - [ Crowd Cheering ]
我們愛你，指揮官
[ Woman ] We love you, Commander !
永不放棄，永不投降！
- Never give up, never-- - [ Audience In Unison ] Never surrender !
別管那些火炮，全力上啊
Damn the resonance cannons, full speed ahead ! Huh ?
指揮官和他的飛行員會
[ Emcee ] The Commander and his crew will be signing autographs...
在可樂機旁邊的 演播台C和B為大家簽名
on Imperial decks "C" and "B" near the Coke machines.
哇，永遠探險，夥計！
[ Man ] Whoo ! Quest forever, man !
對不起，飛行員們過來了
Excuse me, pardon me. Crew member coming through.
影迷，是嗎？嘿，格溫
嘿，夥計
- Fans, right ? Hey, Gwen. - Oh, hey, man.
非常感謝今天你給我們做的介紹
I want to thank you for that nice intro you gave us today.
嗯， 夥計
- Um-- - Guy.
你也許不認識我了 是因為我戴了眼鏡
You probably don't remember me, do you ? It's the sunglasses, right ?
我在82年的81集裡演過戲
I was on the show in '82, episode 81.
第一段插播的廣告還沒開始 我就被怪物殺掉了，唉！
Got killed by a lava monster before the first commercial. Aaah !
聽著，也許我也可以坐在那裡，簽幾個名
Listen, uh-- Maybe I could sit in and, uh, sign a couple autographs ?
上帝做證，我會為你報仇
By Grabthar's hammer, by the sons of Warvan, I shall avenge you !
下一個
- By Grabthar's-- - Next.
如果我再向左移一英吋 怪物就已經殺掉我了
Had I moved an inch to the left, the beast would have killed me.
另一方面，我的船員正處在危險之中 你知道該怎麼做？
- On the other hand, my crew was in danger. - How did you know what to do ?
沒有我的這些船員 我就不是一個指揮官了
Come on ! Without my crew, I'm not a commander, huh ?
我想我們都記得那個恩諾克第七星系的 怪物後來怎麼樣了，對吧
I think we all remember what happened to that beast on Enok Seven, right ?
[ Crowd Laughing ]
你必須承認，他們確實喜歡他
You've gotta admit, they really do love him.
是，就像他自己喜歡自己一樣
Yeah, almost as much as he loves himself.
對不起，指揮官，嘿！
Excuse me, Commander. Hey !
我在想你是否能幫忙解決一些 我和我的船員之間的爭端
I was wondering if you could help settle a dispute my crew and I seem to be having.
嗯，如果你記得，在「帝勒馬類星體」……
Um, if you remember, uh, in "Quasar Dilemma--"
對不起，打擾一下，夥計
Excuse me for a minute, fellas.
我還沒有明白那個
I hadn't even gotten to the relevant conundrum.
15集「得洛斯第五星系的迷霧」中的謎語
In episode 15, "Mist of Delos Five,"
我有一種感覺你和指揮官之間有點什麼
I got the feeling that you and the Commander kind of had a thing.
是嗎？ 沒有
- Did you ? - No.
我們之間什麼也沒有
The Commander and I never had a thing.
好吧，是他這樣說的
Well that's her story.
對不起
Excuse me.
格溫，格溫
Gwen. Gwen.
格溫
Gwen.
指揮官 ，對不起
- Commander. - Excuse me.
我有事要和你說，十萬火急
I must speak to you. It is a matter of supreme importance.
我們是從卡拉圖星雲來的賽米安人
We are Thermians from the Klatu Nebula...
我們需要你們的幫助
and we... need your help.
哦，哦
Oh, oh, oh.
是和明天的演出有關嗎？
Is this about that gig tomorrow ?
你和我的經紀人談吧 但必須有輛豪華車來接我
Just hammer out the details with my agent, and make sure there's a limo at my house.
上次我做完節目 他們把我塞進了輛豐田車的後座
Last time I did one of these gigs, they shoved me in the back of a Toyota.
記住，說嗯
Remember, mum's the word.
當然，但……嗯
- Certainly, but um-- - Mum.
嗯 嗯 嗯 嗯
- Mum. Mum. - Mum. - Mum.
看那邊，真美啊
Look here. And... beautiful.
麥迪遜，那個陌生星球的星氳
Crewman Madison. The mist of this strange planet...
讓我覺得
is filling my head with such thoughts.
在我認識你以前，我是很聰明的
It was cute when I didn't know you.
你
[ Chuckles ] You--
- [ Chattering, Indistinct ] - [ Laughing ]
[ Giggling ]
[ Man Coughing ]
[ Men Chuckling ]
真是個荒唐的節目 哦，真好笑
What a freak show, man. Oh, this is hilarious.
一群廢物！花15美元來求一個簽名
Bunch of losers ! Beggin' for autographs at 15 bucks a pop.
而那些傢伙已經20年沒演過戲了
- [ Toilet Flushes ] - These guys haven't had a real acting job for 20 years.
他們就這點能耐，耐思密斯在哪裡？
- This is all they've got. - Did you check out Nesmith ?
他被那些認為 他是真的太空指揮官的白癡纏著
He actually gets off on those retards thinking he's a space commander !
是啊，他的朋友們呢？我知道！
- Yeah ! Oh, and his friends ? - I know !
他們也不能容忍他！ 你聽到他們剛才在那邊揶揄他嗎？
They can't stand him ! Did you hear them ragging on him in there ?
老兄，他根本不知道 甚至對他的朋友來說，他也是個笑柄
Dude, he has no idea he's a laughingstock, even to his buddies.
他真可憐！ 哦，算了吧
- He's pathetic ! - Ooh, come on, come on.
《銀河探險》的演員差不多都來了
The Galaxy Quest Dancers are almost on.
喔，全力衝刺，上尉
Whoo ! Full speed ahead, Lieutenant.
嘿，指揮官
Hey, Commander, uh, so, as I was saying,
在「類星體的困境」中， 你使用了控制B的後備動力
in "The Quasar Dilemma," remember, you used the auxiliary of deck B--
你怎麼能不怕輻射來到控制台B呢？
could you get this-- deck B for gamma override.
問題是，是不是設計圖清楚地顯示
The thing is is that online blueprints clearly indicate...
甲板B是獨立於導航模型的嗎？
that deck B is independent of the guidance matrix.
我們想知道，問題出在哪裡
So, we were wondering just where the error lies in that.
這只是個電視節目，僅此而已
It's just a television show. That's all, okay ?
是沒錯,不過..
[ Chuckles ] Right, but--
我們想知道，是不是量子流……
'Cause we were wondering if the quantum flux-- Now, just listen on this--
根本沒有量子流
There is no quantum flux !
沒有什麼後備動力， 沒有他媽的，飛船！
There's no auxiliary. There's no goddamn ship !
你明白了嗎？
You got it ?
他要去哪裡?
- [ Crowd Murmuring ] - [ Man ] Where's he going ?
我說真的，亞力克斯
I mean it. I mean it, Alex.
我從來沒見過他對一個影迷這麼失態
I've never seen him lose it like that. Not to a fan.
我是說，這很奇怪
I mean, it was just weird.
格溫，我說了好幾年了
Gwen, I have said it for years.
他的精神狀態很不穩定
He's mentally unstable.
我很擔心
[ Sighs ] l-- I'm worried.
這根本不像他
It just was not like him.
[ TV: Man Grunting ]
[ TV: Gunfire ]
[ Channels Changing ]
只要出現不正義的事
As long as there is injustice,
不管是撻干帝那的孩子叫救命
whenever a Targathian baby cries out,
或是星海中的求救信號
- wherever a distress signal sounds among the stars, - [ Reciting Along ]
我們都會出現 偉大的飛船，偉大的船員
-we'll be there-- this fine ship, this fine crew. -This fine ship, this fine crew.
永不放棄，永不妥協
- Never give up and never surrender. - Never give up.
永不妥協
Never surrender.
[ Knocking ]
- [ Knocking Continues ] - [ Moaning Softly ]
[ Groans ]
需要幫忙嗎？ 先生，我想你們嚴重違約了
- Can I help you ? - Sir, I understand this is a terrible breach in protocol--
你們不能到我家來 請聽我說
- You guys shouldn't come to my house, man. - I beg you to hear our plea.
我們是從卡拉圖星雲來的賽米安人
We are Thermians from the Klatu Nebula.
我們的人民正被
Our people are being systematically hunted and slaughtered...
法圖格雷的薩理斯大規模的屠殺
by Roth'h'ar Sarris of Fatu-Krey.
我們的要去參加談判 為了這，我們付出了慘痛的代價
We are to meet in negotiation. However, our efforts in this regard have been disastrous.
指揮官，你是我們最後的希望
Please, Commander. You are our last hope.
[ Chuckles ]
我們的轎車很安全
- We have secured our limousine. - What ?
哦，哦，哦
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
事情是這樣的，嗯
Um, it's the thing for the thing that's, um--
也許我該穿條褲子
[ Chuckles ] Maybe I should get some pants on.
進來吧
Come on in.
指揮官
- [ Groans ] - Commander,
我必須說能夠這樣站在你面前
I must say that standing here in your presence...
是我一生最大的榮幸
is the greatest honor we could have ever hoped to achieve in our lifetimes.
我很感激
That's-- I really appreciate that.
你們能幫我找另一隻鞋嗎？
Would you guys look for another shoe that looks like this, please ?
[ Groans ]
先生，我是高級軍需官朗克
Sir, I am Lahnk, senior requisition officer.
在我們上船之前，我想知道 我們是否帶齊了必需品
Before we travel to the ship, please let me know if you have any requirements.
武器，記錄片，人員？ 可口可樂，你們有嗎？
- Weapons, documents, personnel ? - Um, a Coca-Cola ? Do you have one of those ?
先生，我是泰博
- Sir, I am Teb. - [ Chuckles ]
我想先介紹一下我們兩族人之間的歷史
I would like to explain the history between our people...
和薩理斯的統治 嘿，你好嗎？
- and the Sarris Dominion in greater detail. - Hey, how ya doin' ?
在星雲大爆炸後的5百萬年裡
In the five million years following the Great Nebula Burst,
我們的人…… 你叫什麼？
- our people were one p-- - What's your name ?
她不會說話嗎？ 她的翻譯器壞了
- Doesn't she talk ? - Her translator is broken.
[ Shrieks ]
好的
- [ Opens Soda Can ] - Okeydokey.
夥計們，我昨天睡得很晚
和一個Kreemorian Fangor畜生在一起
You know, guys, I had a late night with a Kreemorian Fangor beast,
我想先打個盹
so I'm gonna just shut my eyes for a bit.
你繼續，你說的我都能聽見
Go on. You know. I'm listening to everything you say, okay ?
在星雲大爆炸後的5百萬年裡
In the five million years following the Great Nebula Burst,
我們是一族人
our people were one people.
後來，扎克拖人移民過來 再後來梅利沙人也來了
But then came the Zactor Migration, and then the Melosian Shift,
到處充斥著不滿和爭執
dark period of discontent once spread through the land.
自己人起了爭鬥，真愚蠢
Fighting among Treeb sects and Largoths-- ah, the foolishness.
就在那時薩理斯……
And it was in this time of dissension that Sarris--
[ Barking ]
指揮官。指揮官。 嗯
- [ Laliari ] Commander. Commander. - Hmm.
抱歉叫醒你，但指揮台叫你
I'm sorry to wake you, sir, but your presence is requested on the command deck.
[ Grunts ]
先生，薩理斯約過界限了
- Sir, Sarris has moved the deadline. - [ Groans ]
我們正在尼－德爾區域接近他的船
We are approaching his ship at the Ni-delta now.
他想聽我們的答覆
He wants an answer to his proposal.
我在車裡聽懂一些 薩理斯是壞人，是嗎？
Yeah, I got most of it in the car. Sarris is the bad guy, right ?
是的，他們確實很壞
Oh, yes, sir. He's a very bad man indeed.
他折磨我們的科學家 強迫我們開採砷化鎵礦
He has tortured our scientists, put us to work in the gallium arsenide mines,
為滿足他下流的目的 專門掠奪我們的女性
- Mm-hmm. - captured our females for his own demented purposes--
是，我明白了，你們有劇本嗎？ 或者是要我即興發揮？
Yeah, yeah, I got the picture. Do you have pages or do you just want me to wing this ?
我不太明白你 指揮官
- I am not sure I understand you. - [ Mathesar ] Commander.
歡迎來到保護者2號
- Welcome to the Protector Two. - Good to see ya.
你想穿上制服嗎？ 不
- Would you like to don your uniform ? - I'd like to skip that.
15分鐘前，我從范努斯買的這個，這樣行嗎？
I got this gig in Van Nuys in about a quarter of an hour. Is that all right ?
隨便您 先生，是薩理斯
- As you wish. - Sir, it's Sarris.
他來了
He's here.
將軍我收到消息賽米安人 任命了一個新指揮官
General, I just received word the Thermians have appointed a new commander...
來和我們談判
to handle the negotiations.
什麼？
What ?
[ Moaning ]
很好，一般這都是用車庫裡的夾板做的
This is great. You know, usually it's just cardboard walls in a garage.
先生，很抱歉 我們正在低能量模式下運行
- Sir, we apologize for operating in low-power mode, - Oh. Oooh.
但我們正經過反射折曲區域 這很接近銀河的軸心
but we are experiencing a reflective flex field this close to the galactic axis.
你知道，我想要什麼？ 一個杯架和幾片止痛藥
You know what I could use ? A cup holder and a couple of Advil.
5秒鐘後，我們就接近了，先生要減速嗎？
We're approaching in five ticks, sir. Command to slow ?
放在2號屏幕上
Set it on screen saver two.
因為我們
[ Chuckles ] Because we, you know-- We gotta--
抱歉破壞了這裡的氣氛
[ Groans ] Oh, I'm sorry to break the mood here.
減速到兩馬克，上尉
Um, slow it down to mark two, Lieutenant.
我能感到恐懼
[ Sarris Over Speaker ] I see fear.
很正常 嗯
- That is expected. - Mm-hmm.
他們有了個新指揮官 很好
- Ahh, they bring a new commander. - It's good.
這就是我的要求 真令人害怕，我是說，他看起來
- Here are my demands. - It's scary. I mean, you know, he looks...
如果你們不能滿足我的要求
- And if I do not hear what I like, - real.
就會有流血
then there will be blood...
還有你們想像不到的痛苦！
and pain as you cannot imagine !
首先，我要 醉酒的後果
- First, I require... - Backwash.
歐米茄13
the Omega 13.
第二，我要一個技師
Second, I will require a technician--
好的，我們全速啟動 藍色粒子炮，紅色粒子炮
Okeydokey. Let's fire blue particle cannons full. Red particle cannons full.
向他的左右兩邊開炮
Gannet magnets, fire them left and right.
把他們趕到斜槽上去 我們在那裡等他們
And let 'em run all chutes. And while you're at it,
你為什麼不狠狠揍他們，殺手？
why don't you toss that at 'em, killer ?
那就足夠對付那個龍蝦腦袋了，是嗎？
That should take care of old lobster head, shouldn't it ?
[ Chuckles ]
指揮官，你去哪裡？
Commander, where are you going ?
回家 你是說，地球？
- Home. - You-- You mean Earth ?
是的，我要回地球，小子
Yeah, Earth. I need to get back to Earth, kids.
但談判怎麼辦？ 你已經向他開火了
But the negotiation. You-You fired on him.
是，萬歲！ 你們的星球叫什麼來著？賽米安
- Yeah, yeah. Long live-- What was your planet called ? - Thermia.
萬歲賽米安，這邊走嗎？ 但如果薩理斯沒死怎麼辦？
- Long live Thermia. This way ? - But what if Sarris survives ?
不可能吧，我給了他兩炮了 他的飛船很堅固
- I doubt it. I gave him both barrels. - He has a very powerful ship.
如果那傢伙還有什麼問題的話 打電話給我
If you got any more problems with the guy, just give me a call.
喔！
- [ Bangs Step ] - Ow !
一個星際對講器 一個什麼？
- An interstellar vox. - A what ? Hey.
我們怎麼感謝你呢？指揮官
- [ Beeping ] - How can we thank you, Commander ?
你拯救了我們的人民
You-- You have saved our people.
哦，好了，你們表現得很好，真的很好
Yeah. Okay. You know, you kids have been great. You really have.
這東西看起來真不錯 喂？？
This thing is real lookin'. Yoo-hoo. Hello ? [ Chuckles ]
嘿，我的轎車呢？
Hey ! Where's my limo ?
嗯？
Huh ?
[ Banging ]
[ Sloshing ]
[ Groans ]
[ Banging ]
[ Female Voices Harmonizing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Panting ]
拿去吧，我們到過宇宙各地
[ Gwen ] Take it from us. We've been all over the universe.
但我們從來沒見過 像這裡的東西這麼有價值
But we've never seen space-age values like we've seen here at--
電器超市！
Tech Value Electronic Superstore !
上帝作證
[ Monotone ] By Grabthar's hammer,
真便宜
what a savings.
好的
All right !
我們來聽聽NSEA保護者
Yeah. Let's hear it for the N.S.E.A. Protector.
[ Chattering ]
布蘭登，你好嗎？ 指揮官
- Brandon, are you okay ? - Commander.
抱歉
My apologies.
關於那次旅行
Evidently, we had a little miscommunication regarding...
the voyage.
你沒去
That you didn't show up.
[ Panting ]
他又這樣了 你來了很好
- He did it again. - [ Man Over P.A. ] Thank you for coming out.
你知道幾點了嗎？ 你還記得要來嗎？
Do you know what time it is ? Why do you even bother to show up at all ?
不…不是現在 我去過那裡，夥計們
N-N-N-Not now. Guys, I was there.
我在那裡，記得昨天見面會上
I was up there. Remember yesterday at the convention ?
有幾個穿得像外星人得傢伙嗎？ 他們真是外星人
Those people dressed like aliens ? They were aliens.
他們是特米特人或者說是達爾馬特人
They were Termites or Dalmatians. I can't really remember 'cause I was hungover.
他們造的飛船很出色
But what they built was extraordinary.
那是個大飛船，我不得不去幫他們 打一個叫薩理斯的傢伙 我狠狠教訓了他一頓
It was a huge spaceship. I got to fight this guy named Sarris and I kicked his ass.
我知道你們怎麼想，我有證據 他們給了我這個
I know what you're thinkin'. But I can prove it. They gave me this.
不不不…… 你能用這個和太空裡的人交談嗎？
No, no, no, no, no. But can you talk to people in space on those ?
保護者，這是指揮官
Protector, this is the commander. Over.
哦，看在上帝份上 我們走吧
- Oh, for God's sake. - That's it. It's time to go !
這個不是我那個
This isn't mine.
那個孩子在哪兒？ 什麼？指揮官
- That kid. Where's that kid ? - Begging your pardon, Commander ?
壞消息，薩理斯還活著
We come with news. Sarris lives.
你走了之後，他跑掉了
聽著，告訴他們
- He was able upon your departure to make an escape. - Listen. Tell them.
但是，他聯絡我們說要投降
- However, he has contacted us and wishes to negotiate a surrender. - Sarris.
他懇求你來協助我們談判條件
We humbly implore you to come and negotiate the terms.
嗯？他們要我回去？ 你們要我回去？
Huh ? They want me back ? You want me back ?
太神奇了，他們要我回去 我想你們和我一起去，可以嗎？
Is this amazing ? They want me back, and I want you guys to go with me. Please ?
想想看，走吧，好阿！
Think about it. Let's go. Yes !
你去嗎？
You're-- You're goin' ?
亞歷山大，這不是 我沒開玩笑
Alexander, this is not-- I'm not kiddin' here.
這不是什麼惡作劇，我沒開玩笑
This isn't some kind of prank. I'm not kiddin'.
夥計們，聽啊，來吧，格溫
No, guys, guys, listen. Come on. Gwen, Gwen, Gwen.
停一停，到這邊來 你知道我的，我不是瘋子
Stop. Come here. You know me, and I'm a lot of things, but am I crazy ?
你們怎麼對我是一回事
You know, it's one thing to treat us this way.
你們怎麼對影迷又是另一回事
It's another thing to do it to your fans.
她不是影迷，她是特米特人
She's not a fan. This is-- This is a Termite !
你該讓我揍他一頓
You should've just let me hit him.
孩子們，你們不該想那麼多
Boy, I didn't know you could get that loaded.
我想我們該抓住這個機會
I think we should've just taken the gig.
我意思是，誰知道下次他會要我們做什麼？
I mean, who knows the next time he'll ask us ?
弗來德，他醉了 你認為他真的是在說一個話兒嗎？
Fred, he was drunk. Do you really think he was talking about a job ?
但你和你媽媽一起住 賈森來了嗎？
- But you live with your mother. - Did Jason come through here ?
是的，他在。夥計們
Yeah, he's in there. Hey, guys.
我們準備去了
Ah. We are coming too.
你們都去嗎 是的，我們都願意去
- All of you wish to go to the ship ? - Yes, we wish to go to the ship.
你看，我們要不一起工作 要不就不工作
You see, we work together, or not at all.
太好了，如果你們改變主意了 指揮官讓我繼續傳送
Wonderful. The commander had me continue transmission in case you changed your mind.
保護者，請求4個太空繭 我也去
- Protector, requesting four interstellar-- - Me too.
5個，立即出發
five pods for immediate departure.
[ Hum Resonating ]
夥計們
Guys.
夥計們 你們到達飛船時
- Guys. - I look forward to meeting you all...
我很想趕快見到你們
in person when you arrive at the ship.
傳送結束
- End transmission. - [ Whooshing ]
哦，天哪
- [ Liquid Sloshing ] - Oh, my God.
有誰覺得有變化嗎？
- [ Whooshing ] - Anybody got any change ?
[ Exhales ]
[ Shrieking In The Distance ]
[ Shrieking Continues ]
[ Instruments Whirring ]
[ Whirring ]
[ Shrieking Continues ]
萬分抱歉
Our most sincere apologies.
我們忘記開外貌轉換器了…… 你們來啦
- We forgot about our appearance generators. - You guys came.
誰想參觀一下
Who wants the grand tour ?
[ Screaming ]
還有其他人嗎？
- [ Screaming Stops ] - Anybody else ?
太了不起了
That was a hell of a thing.
他們怎麼了 我不知道，來吧
- What's wrong with them ? - I don't know. Come on.
對了，夥計們 繼續搖搖腦袋，那樣會好點
That's right, guys. Keep shaking it off. It gets better.
來點口香糖，那樣會好點 我們在哪兒？
- Try some gum. It helps. - Where are we ?
伽馬區的23分區 前面房間有地圖
The twenty-third quadrant of the gamma sector. There's a map in the forward room.
來，我指給你們看
I'll show you. Come on.
歡迎，朋友們 這是馬沙，他們的領袖
- Welcome, my friends. - This is Mathesar. He's their leader.
我是馬西薩，代表所有人
I am Mathesar. On behalf of all my people,
萬分感謝你們
I wish to thank you from the deepest place in our hearts.
馬西薩，這是我的船員們
Mathesar, this is, uh, my crew.
拉扎羅斯博士
Dr. Lazarus.
[ Mathesar's Crew Whispering ] Dr. Lazarus. Dr. Lazarus.
麥迪遜上尉
Lieutenant Madison.
[ Whispering ] Lieutenant Madison.
小拉熱多，你長大了
Young Laredo, how you've grown.
小拉熱多
Young Laredo.
技師陳中士
Tech Sergeant Chen.
[ Mathesar's Crew ] Tech Sergeant Chen. Tech Sergeant Chen.
全體船員都在了
C-Crew man number-- Guy.
夥計們
Guy.
你們認識我們？
You... know us ?
[ Chuckling ]
自從我們第一次接收到你們的記錄片
I don't believe there is a man, woman or child on my planet who does not.
我們星球上的人就都認識你們了
Since we first received transmission of your historical documents,
我們仔細研究了你們的所有任務和戰略
we have studied every facet of your missions and strategies.
你們一直在看那個節目？ 上尉，是歷史記錄片
- You've been watchin' the show ? - Lieutenant, historical documents.
歷史記錄片？ 是
- H-Historical documents from out here ? - [ Mathesar ] Yes.
過去的幾百年，我們一直處於混亂當中
The past hundred years our society had fallen into disarray.
我們的目標，我們的價值觀全部打破了 但自從轉播了你們的記錄片後
Our goals, our values had become scattered. But since the transmission,
我們重塑了整個社會的所有層面
- we have modeled every aspect of our society... - [ Grunts ]
你們的榜樣力量拯救了我們
from your example, and it has saved us.
你們在困境中表現的 勇氣，團隊精神和友誼
Your courage and teamwork and friendship through adversity--
實際上，你環眼四顧
In fact, all you see around you has been taken from the lessons...
所有的人都從這些記錄片中學到了很多
garnered from the historical documents.
這是只太空船嗎？
- Is this a-- a spaceship ? - [ Jason ] No.
不，是太空港
This is a star port for the ship.
你們想看看飛船嗎？
Would you guys like to see the ship ?
[ Door Whooshing ]
[ Banging, Air Rushing Outside ]
天哪
[ Alexander ] Oh, my God !
這是真的
It's real.
[ Mathesar ] The generator room.
鈹合金球
The beryllium sphere, of course.
我們繼續
And as we continue--
醫療倉在左邊
The medical quarters are to the left.
我們在複製你們的細胞時出了點問題
We went through some trouble duplicating your cellular regeneration--
賈森，你把我們帶到了哪兒 我們在這要幹什麼？
- Jason, what have you got us into ? - What are we doing here ?
地板真乾淨 我們是來談判的，斯利斯投降了
- Wow, the floors are so clean. - We're just here to negotiate this guy Sarris' surrender.
不算什麼 接著就是器官構造室
- It's no big deal. - And the organ fabrication chamber is coming along nicely.
還不算什麼嗎？
It's no big deal ?
你瘋了嗎？ 我們必須離開這裡
- Are you crazy ? We have to get out of here. - Oh, come on, guys.
賈森，我們是演員，不是宇航員
Jason, we are actors, not astronauts.
你們想回家嗎？說出來啊 說出來，我們就回家
You guys wanna go home ? Say the word, we'll go home.
回家去付我們的帳單，  我們的魚
Pay our bills, feed our fish,
看著電視直到睡覺 你們會錯過這裡所有的一切
fall asleep in front of the TV and miss out on all of this.
說啊，你們希望這樣嗎？有人希望嗎？
Come on. Do you guys wanna do that ? Anybody ?
格溫，我們是在太空裡！
Gwen, come on. Look at where we are. We're in space.
亞歷山大，這是我們一生夢寐以求的角色 你想離開？
Alexander, this is the role of a lifetime. You guys wanna leave ?
我們幫你們準備了你們最喜歡吃的東西
We have enjoyed preparing many of your esoteric dishes.
我們只需要一些簡單的東西，比如三明治
Your Monte Cristo sandwich is a current favorite among the adventurous.
這是最大的宿舍
The main barracks.
[ Drums Play Cadence ]
請便
At ease.
這就像火中澆油
It's like throwing gasoline on a flame.
什麼？
What ?
我只是在說一些廢話
I'm just jazzed about being on the show, man.
請就座
[ Mathesar ] lf you would all take your positions.
什麼？ 夥計
- [ Gwen ] Our what ? - Guys.
哦 哦
- Oh. Oh. - Oh. - Oh, wh-- Hmm.
看那個
Look, this thingy.
我記得我已經設計成功了
I remember-- I remember I had it all worked out.
這是前進,這是後退
This is forward. This is back.
[ Hum Resonating, Whooshes ]
指揮官，在這個歷史性的時刻 你的一些船員希望能見到你
Commander, some of the crew has requested to be present at this historic event.
當然，把他們帶進來
Sure. Bring 'em in.
[ Shrilling ]
沒有壓力，呃？ 很高興我不是指揮官
[ Chuckles ] No pressure, huh ? Glad I ain't the commander.
拉來多，把我們帶出去
Laredo, take us out.
對不起？
- Excuse me ? - [ Chuckles ]
他們模仿你設計了這些遙控器
They designed those controls after watching you.
把船弄出來. 好的,好的
- Take her out. - [ Clears Throat ] Right, right.
沒問題
Okay.
好的
Right.
好的, 帶她弄出來
Right. Take her out.
[ Banging ]
- [ Air Rushing ] - [ Spaceship Revving ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Spaceship Rising ]
好
Okay.
你必須向右邊
Y-you gotta move to the right.
平行 你坐下來好嗎？坐下，你想來駕船？
- Hit parallel. - Would you sit your ass down ? Sit ! You wanna drive ?
[ Metal Scraping ]
- [ Nervous Chuckle ] - [ High-Pitched Scraping ]
[ Scraping Stops ]
哦，嗯
牛排怎麼樣，指揮官？
How are you enjoying your steak, Commander ?
很好，好像是用玉米飼料 養出來的艾奧瓦牛
I'm really enjoying it. This is like corn-fed lowa beef.
是的，我們設計了食物合成的程序
Yes. We programmed the food synthesizer...
我們按照你們各自的出生地，安排了食譜
for each of you based on the regional menu of your birthplace.
我不在乎這個，我只知道味道很好
[ Jason ] I don't care where you did it. It tastes great !
拉扎羅斯博士 喜歡你的牛排嗎？
Are you enjoying your Kep-mok bloodticks, Dr. Lazarus ?
就像我媽媽做的
Just like Mother used to make.
告訴我，馬西薩
So, um-- [ Groans ] Tell me, Mathesar.
那個我們要去見的薩理斯
This Sarris person that we're flying to meet,
他到底想要幹嗎？
- what does he want, exactly ? - [ Gagging ]
他聽過歐米茄13
He heard about the device-- the Omega 13.
呃，那是用來幹嗎的？
Um, what is it ? What does it do ?
我們不知道
We don't know.
我們還希望你能告訴我們呢
We were hoping you could enlighten us.
[ Nervous Chuckle ]
歐米茄13
Oh. The Omega 13 device.
是我們在一個外星星球上發現的 我們也不知道是用來幹嗎的
We found that on an alien planet. We don't know what it does either.
你們為何不打開它 看看到底是用來幹嗎的
- [ Gasps ] - Why don't you just turn it on and see what it does ?
- [ Shrills ] - [ Laughs ]
在它的中心有個 擁有不可思議能量的反應堆
It has at its heart a reactor capable of unthinkable energy.
如果我們的操作有誤的話
If we were mistaken in our construction, the device would...
這個裝置就會發生分子爆炸 引起連鎖反應
act as a molecular explosive, causing a chain reaction...
甚至會毀滅整個宇宙
that would obliterate all matter in the universe.
薩理斯 聽過有關 這個歷史記錄片的事情嗎？
Has Sarris ever seen any of the, uh, historical records ?
不，沒聽過
No, thank God, he has not.
那，他聽過歐米茄13嗎？
Oh. So how does he know about the Omega 13 device ?
我們以前那個指揮官不夠堅強
Our former commander was not... strong.
以前的指揮官？
Former commander ?
對不起，我們該給你看
I am sorry. You deserve to be shown.
這個從薩理斯船上偷帶過來的錄像帶
The tape was smuggled off of Sarris' ship.
原來，一個我們自己的人試過做指揮官
Originally, one of our own tried to lead.
我等了三天，就只這些了嗎？
Is that all ? After three days of this,
你還需要來到刺激嗎？
you still require... incentive ?
- [ Shrieking ] - [ Electrical Buzzing ]
我已經告訴你所有我知道的了
[ Female ] I have told you all I know.
如果你還有點仁慈的話，讓我死吧
If you have any mercy within you, please, let me die.
當我聽厭了你的聲音，你就得死
[ Sarris ] When I grow weary of the noises you make, you shall die.
[ Electrical Buzzing ]
等一下，你不能走
Wait a minute, guys. Come on. Hold on a minute. You just can't leave.
讓我想想，他需要考慮
- Give me some time to think. - He wants to think.
賈森，那是騙局，根本沒什麼好想的
No, Jason, that's a wrap. There's nothing to think about.
我根本不該在這兒，我是編外的船員 只是個跑龍套的
I'm not even supposed to be here. I'm just crewman number six. I'm expendable.
我是在那一集中 那個為顯示情況危急 而被安排死掉的傢伙
I'm the guy in the episode who dies to prove the situation is serious. I gotta get out.
指揮官？我們必須準備太空繭了 我的船員要離開了
- Commander ? - We gotta prepare the pods for my crew's departure.
對不起，我們現在不能發射太空繭
Begging your commander's pardon, sir. We can't launch pods at the moment.
薩理斯會炸掉任何離開飛船的物體 薩理斯？
- Sarris will surely detonate any objects leaving the ship. - Sarris ?
是的，他在這裡 你必須到指揮台去
Yes, sir. He's here now. Your presence is required on the command deck.
[ Stammers ]
這裡沒有人了
There's nobody here.
雖然我們的科學家都很有才能
While my people are talented scientists,
但我們在戰術偽裝的技術上
our attempt to operate our own technologies...
一直很糟糕
under tactical simulation have been disastrous.
薩理斯在Zeta波段上，馬西薩
- I have raised Sarris on zeta frequency. - [ Jason ] Mathesar--
我們又見面了，指揮官
We meet again, Commander.
你好，薩理斯
Hello, Sarris. How you doin' ?
很好
Better than my lieutenant.
上次我們碰面時，我的上尉沒能
He failed to activate the ship's neutron armor as quickly as I'd hoped...
像我希望的那樣及時啟動中子防護甲
on our last encounter.
哦，我對以前發生的事很抱歉
Yeah, well, you know, I'd like to say I'm real sorry about what happened before.
純粹是個誤會
The whole thing was just-- just a misunderstanding.
把那個裝置給我
Deliver the device to me,
要不我就摧毀你的飛船
or I will destroy your ship.
是，我們很樂意
You know, um, we'd like do that,
不過說真的，我們不知道那是什麼東西 甚至它在哪裡我們也不知道
but frankly, Sarris, sir, we don't know what it is or even where it is.
你只有10秒鐘
You have ten seconds !
10秒鐘？
I don't-- Ten seconds ? I don't-- There--
好吧，他媽的，我放棄，我把它給你
You know-- Okay. Gosh darn it, I give up. It's yours. You can have it.
你必須給我一分鐘讓我放到盒子裡 怎麼樣？
You have to give me a minute to put it in a box for you, okay ?
格溫
- Gwen. [ Clicks Tongue ] - [ Groans ]
別慌，我以前對付過那傢伙 他又蠢又醜，到這邊來
Don't panic. I've dealt with this guy before. He's as stupid as he is ugly. Come here.
賈森， 不是現在，格溫，坐下來
- Jason. - Not now, Gwen. Sit, sit, sit, sit.
我們狠狠揍他一頓，好嗎？
We're gonna send everything we can at him, all right ?
賈森 現在不行
- [ Gwen ] Jason. - Not now, Gwen !
按下那個紅色按鈕 狠狠揍他一頓，好嗎？
Push these red buttons and send everything we have towards him, okay ?
好吧 好吧，格溫
- Okay. - All right, Gwen. [ Clears Throat ]
把圖像接過來 好的，我告訴你，他就在你面前
- Put me back on with him. - Well, I'm trying to tell you, you are back with him.
也許我並不是又蠢又醜，指揮官
Perhaps I'm not as stupid as I am ugly, Commander.
我給了你「殺」的手勢
I gave you the... "kill" gesture.
沒，你給了「我們完了」的手勢
No, you gave me the "we're dead" signal.
我那時是表示同意
I was agreeing with you. Like I know where the hold button is.
嘿，夥計們
[ Guy ] Hey, guys.
有個紅顏色的物體
- [ Beeping On Monitor ] - There's a red, uh, thingy...
在向那個綠色的物體靠近
movin' toward the green thingy.
什麼？ 紅顏色的物體在向綠色的物體靠近
- What ? - Red thingy movin' toward the green thingy.
我想，我們就是那個綠色物體
I think-- I think we're the green thingy.
有個小禮物，指揮官
A little present for you, Commander.
我們快離開離開這裡 快轉彎，快，快
We gotta get out of here. Move this ship. Turn it. Move ! Let's go !
[ Gwen Screaming ]
[ Explosion ]
- [ Explosion ] - [ Screams ]
湯米，我們走，離開這裡！ 賈森，我該怎麼辦？
- Tommy, let's go ! Get us out of here ! - Jason, what do I do ?
快走，走！
Go, go, go !
[ Screaming ]
哇喔！
他們也轉彎了，他們過來了
They're turning. They're coming !
全速向前衝
Thrust ahead, full !
開火
Fire at will.
快點啊，湯米
- [ Explosion ] - Go faster, Tommy !
我已經最快了！ 它還跟在我們後面
- I'm going as fast as I can ! - She's still behind us !
啟動渦輪，像我常說的那樣
Well, uh, uh, press turbo. I'm always saying, "Press the turbo," right ?
哦，在這裡 按住它
- Oh, it's here. Right here. - Press it and hold it down.
[ Explosion ]
哇喔！
- [ Whooshing ] - Whoo !
敵人在加速
[ Computerized Voice ] The enemy is matching velocity.
敵人在加速 我第一次聽到這句台詞
- Enemy is matching velocity. - We heard it the first time !
哦，天哪，我在複述電腦的話
Gosh, I'm doing it. I'm repeating the darn computer.
嘿，夥計們，電腦在告訴我
Hi, guys. Listen. They're tellin' me...
發動機已經承受不了了
the, uh-- the generators won't take it.
飛船要散架啦
The ship is breakin' apart and all that.
僅供參考
Just F.Y.I.
我們必須停下來 停下來就完了。湯米，按住渦輪按鈕啊
- We've gotta stop ! - We stop and we die. Tommy, just hold that down.
你不要按下渦輪按鈕 那是快速推進用的
- You don't hold the turbo down. It's for quick boosts ! - Oh, like you know.
[ Turbo Shutting Down, Sputtering ]
我記得那聲音
- [ Alarm Blaring ] - [ Gwen ] I remember that sound.
那是個不祥的聲音
That's a bad sound.
等等，我們也許能在那片雲那邊甩掉他們
Wait, wait, wait, wait. We might be able to lose them in this cloud here.
我不認為那是片雲
Oh, I don't-- I don't think that's a cloud.
馬西薩，那是什麼？ 那是12185年的宇宙大戰留下的雷區
- Mathesar, what is this ? - Tothian minefield left standing from the Great War of 12185.
啊，天哪！
Oh, God ! [ Screams ] Whoo !
[ Grunting, Screams ]
- [ Explosion ] - [ Whimpering ]
你是不是能一個雷也別碰上？
Could you possibly try not to hit every single one ?
對不起，它在向我們飄過來 我想一定是有磁性
Sorry, man. They're driftin' towards us ! I think they're magnetic !
還前進嗎，先生？
Continue forward, sir ?
耐心點，上尉
Patience, Lieutenant.
耐心
Patience.
我們必須停下來 我們快過去了
- We've gotta stop ! - We're almost through this.
[ High-Pitched Screaming ]
你還好嗎？ 是的
- You okay ? You all right ? - Yeah.
大家都好嗎？湯米在哪兒？
- [ Groaning ] - Everybody all right ? Where's Tommy ?
哦，老兄 湯米，你好嗎？
- [ Screaming ] Oh, man ! - Tommy ! You all right ?
不好，我的胳膊骨折了 別碰我，別碰我胳膊
No, my arm is broke-- No, don't touch it. Don't touch it.
我帶他去醫務室 謝謝，馬西薩
- I'll take him to medical quarters. - Thanks, Mathesar.
[ Screaming ]
亞力克斯，你去哪兒？
Alex, where are you going ?
看看有沒有酒吧
To see if there's a pub.
前進推動軸87％損壞
[ Computer ] Forward thruster shaft: 87 percent damage.
矢量防護裝置96％損壞
Aft vector guards: 96 percent damage.
32，34，40區結構性破裂
Structural breaches in quadrants 32, 34, 40--
發動機怎麼樣？
- What about the engines ? - Forward thruster shaft:
前進推動軸87％損壞 電腦，發動機怎麼樣了？
- 87 percent damage. - Computer, what about the engines ?
我們沒動力了 鈹球被壓斷裂了
- Why don't we have power ? - The beryllium sphere has fractured under stress.
斷了？ 能修好嗎？
- It's fractured. - Can it be repaired ?
計算機，能修好嗎？ 鈹金球損壞，無法修復
- Computer, can it be repaired ? - Damage to beryllium sphere: irreparable.
必須找到新的鈹金 我們要再找一個來
- New source of beryllium must be secured. - We need another one.
你弄壞了飛船，你把該死的飛船弄壞了
You broke the ship. You broke the bloody ship.
呃，啊
Eh, ah-- [ Clears Throat ]
計算機，船上有備用的鈹金球嗎？
Computer, is there a replacement beryllium sphere on board ?
沒有，沒有備用的
Negative. No reserve beryllium sphere exists on board.
看來沒有有備用的了
No, we have no extra beryllium sphere on board.
他媽的...
You know, that is really getting annoying.
在這破飛船上我還有工作要做
Look, I have one job on this lousy ship.
雖然有點傻，但我還是要做，明白嗎？
It's stupid, but I'm gonna do it, okay ?
當然，，沒問題
Sure, no problem.
萬分抱歉，我們讓你們失望了
A thousand apologies. We have failed you.
你們怎麼會讓我們失望呢？
[ Chuckles ] How have you failed us ?
我們看過你們在更危急的 情況下都能轉危為安
We have seen you victorious in much more desperate situations.
是我們的錯，是飛船的錯
The fault must lie with us, with the ship.
不，馬西薩 不是你的錯，也不是飛船的錯
No, Mathesar, it is not your fault, and it's not the ship's fault.
是，是，是，我的錯
It's-It's-It's-It's my fault.
我們，我們並不像你們想像的那樣
-We-We screwed-- -We are not the people you think we are.
我不明白
I don't understand.
在你們的星球上，有沒有電視節目？ 有戲劇，電影嗎？
Didn't you make any TV shows on your planet ? Any theater, films ?
關於你們自己文化的記錄片
The historical documents of your culture.
是，實際上，我們已經 開始學習你們記錄歷史了
Yes, in fact, we have begun to document our history from your example.
不，不是歷史記錄片 我的意思是，那些並不全是記錄片
No, not historical documents. They're not all historical documents. I mean,
你不會認為吉利干島是個……
surely you don't think that Gilligan's Island is a--
那些可憐的傢伙
- [ All Moaning ] - Those poor people.
哦，兄弟
[ Tommy ] Oh, brother.
我們搞砸了
We're screwed.
在你們的星球上沒有人
Is there no one on your planet who behaves in a way...
做一些和事實相反的事情嗎？
that's contrary to reality ?
你是說……
[ Gasping ] You are speaking of--
欺騙.撤謊 欺騙.撤謊
- Deception, lies. - Deception, lies.
我們也是最近和薩理斯打交道時 才對欺騙有了些概念
We have only recently become aware of this concept in our dealings with Sarris.
薩理斯經常嘴上這麼說 做起來又是另一回事
Often, Sarris will say one thing and do another.
許諾我們以仁慈，卻施以毀滅
Promise us mercy, but deliver destruction.
我們花了很大的代價才開始瞭解這個概念
It is a concept we are beginning to learn at some great costs.
你們不是說你們和薩理斯有什麼共同點吧--
But if you are saying that any of you could have traits in common with Sarris--
- [ Laughing ] - [ All Laughing ]
[ Laughing ]
指揮官，我們在附近的星球上發現了鈹金
Hey, Commander, listen. We found some beryllium on a nearby planet.
我們也許能到那裡
We might be able to get there...
只要我們改裝一下我們的太陽能模型
if we reconfigure the solar matrix...
設置成平行向熱推進
in parallel for endothermic propulsion.
你怎麼想？
What do you think ?
我們試試！ 好的！
- We'll do that ! - All right !
這就對了
That's-That's-That's right again.
來吧，擁抱一下
That's-- C-C-Come on. Group hug.
來啊
- Come on. - [ All Murmuring ]
拉扎羅斯博士，但願我沒有違約
Dr. Lazarus, I hope I am not breaching protocol,
我站在你面前覺得很渺小
but I am so very humbled to stand in your presence.
我對你所有的任務都仔細研究過
I have studied your missions extensively.
雖然，我是個賽米亞人 但我是按照你們的人生觀來生活的
Though I am Thermian, I have lived my life by your philosophy,
也遵守馬卡他星球的法律
by the code of the Mak'tar.
很好 上帝作證，拉扎羅斯博士
- Oh, good, that's very nice. - By Grabthar's hammer, Dr. Lazarus.
別這樣，我沒開玩笑 抱歉，先生，我只是……
- Don't do that. I'm not kidding. - I'm sorry, sir, I was just--
別那樣
Just don't.
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
永不放棄，永不妥協
Never give up, never surrender.
拉扎羅斯博士？
Dr. Lazarus ?
這是你要的表面對照轉換器
Here is your surface mapper. I have programmed it to the coordinates...
我把他設計成能匹配足夠密度的鈹金球
of a beryllium sphere of sufficient density.
祝好運，先生 謝謝
- Good luck on your mission, sir. - Thanks.
你幹的很好，湯米
You're doing good, Tommy.
我改主意了，我要回去
I changed my mind. I wanna go back.
你搞得一團糟，現在你想回去了？
After the fuss you made about getting left behind ?
是的，當我認為我是你們的一員的時候 我是這麼想的
Yeah, but that's when I thought I was the crewman...
呆在飛船上 外面有什麼在等著我，這讓我很苦惱
that stays on the ship, and something is up there, and it kills me.
但現在我想只要我們降落在那個星球上
But now I'm thinking I'm the guy who gets killed by some monster...
不出5分鐘，我們就會被某個怪物殺掉
five minutes after we land on the planet.
你不會死的，夥計
You're not gonna die on the planet, Guy.
我不會？ 我姓什麼？
I'm not ? Then what's my last name ?
我不知道
It's, uh, uh-- I don't know.
沒人知道，你知道為什麼嗎？
Nobody knows ! Do you know why ?
因為我只是個跑龍套的，根本不重要
Because my character isn't important enough for a last name,
因為我只有5分鐘的戲，就會被安排死掉
because I'm gonna die five minutes in.
夥計，你有名字的
Guy, you have a last name.
- Do I ? Do I ? - Yes !
你們知道的僅僅是我是那個編外船員
For all you know, I'm just crewman number six.
媽媽！媽媽！
Mommy ! Mommy ! Mommy !
我們到了嗎？
Are we there yet ?
媽媽！ 湯米！
- Mommy ! - [ Jason ] Tommy !
當心！，哦，不！ 停下來！
- Look out ! Oh, no ! - [ Alexander ] Pull out !
是的！
[ Fred Moaning ] Oh, yeah !
[ Moaning Continues ]
別開門，這是個外星球
- [ Beeping ] - [ Guy ] Don't open that ! It's an alien planet !
外面有空氣嗎？你根本不知道！
Is there air ? You don't know !
看上去還行
[ Sniffing, Breathing ] Seems okay.
我們走吧
Here we go.
哪邊，亞歷山大？
[ Jason ] Which way, Alexander ?
[ Beeping ]
這邊！
This way !
等等……不……
Wait. No.
那邊 你拿反了
- That way. - You were holding it upside down.
閉嘴 穿著這些戲服和化妝時
- Shut up. - You know, with all that makeup and stuff,
我實際上覺得你很聰明，當然只一秒種
I actually thought you were smart for a second.
你認為，你會做的更好嗎，拉來多？
You think you could do better, Laredo ?
拉來多沒什麼問題 真是糟透了
- All right with that Laredo stuff. - [ Guy ] Oh, we're so screwed.
好了，好了 我們必須自我克制才能夠完成任務
Come on, come on, come on, if we wanna finish this mission, we have to use self-control.
自制，從一個在戲裡 和女奴、月亮公主鬼混的傢伙
[ Gwen ] "Self-control" ? That's funny, coming from a guy...
嘴裡說出來，很可笑
who slept with every Turekian slave girl and moon princess on the show.
你究竟怎麼了 如果你不是那麼多怪話，你也許已經……
[ Jason ] Ever occur to you, had you been more supportive, you might've been--
哇喔，也許是些採礦設備
[ Alexander ] Wow. Must be some sort of mining facility.
-採礦工人在哪裡？ -這裡曾經發生過不祥的事情
- Where are the miners? - Something bad happened here.
放鬆一點好嗎？
- Will you relax ? - [ Beeping ]
鈹金球在那裡，我們走
There they are. Beryllium spheres. Let's go.
- [ Gasping ] - [ Chattering ]
看
Look at that.
看那邊，他們看上去像小孩子
Would you look at that ? They look like little children.
他們是礦工嗎？
Could they be the miners ?
一定是，他們看上去只有3歲
Sure, they're like three years old.
礦工，不是未成年人
Miners, not minors.
你沒明白我 我不喜歡這樣
- You lost me. - I don't like this.
-我一點也不喜歡他們
-他們超可愛的
- I don't like this at all. - They are so cute.
是的，他們現在很可愛 很快他們就會不客氣了
Sure, they're cute now. In a second, they're gonna get mean.
他們很快就會變得很難看 接著會有幾百萬個出現
They're gonna get ugly somehow, then there's gonna be a million more of them.
看，那個小傢伙受傷了
[ Gasping ] Look. There's a little hurt one.
[ Whimpering ]
哦
Oh.
[ Whimpering Continues ]
嗨.嗨 這裡
Hi. Hi there.
啊！ 噓！
- Ah ! - Shh !
你們看過那場戲嗎？
- Did you guys ever watch the show ? - [ Chattering ]
看過嗎？
See ?
他們會幫助那受傷的小傢伙的
They're gonna help the little hurt one.
[ Whispering ]
[ Snarling ]
我說得沒錯，但我感到很噁心
I'm so sick of being right.
在他們開始殺人之前 我們趕快走吧，等等
- Let's get out of here before one of those things kills Guy. - Wait a minute.
沒拿到鈹金球 我們哪兒也不去，我們需要計劃一下
We're not going anywhere without a beryllium sphere. We need a plan.
弗來德，你去把他們引開
Fred, I need a diversion to clear the compound of those things.
亞力克斯，格溫，和我去拿鈹金球
Then, Alex and Gwen and I will go get a sphere.
湯米，到那山脊上去 看到他們回來，就給我個信號。
Tommy, get up on that ridge, and if you see them come back, give me a signal, all right ?
怎麼聽起來很熟啊
Why does this sound so familiar ?
是81集的台詞
"Assault on Voltareck 3," episode 81.
我們在演第81集？ 那個有火牆，全息圖的一集？
- We're doing episode 81 ? - Whatever. The one with the hologram, the wall of fire.
弗來德怎麼會能發送全息圖呢？
Well, how the hell is Fred supposed to project a hologram ?
我們在81集怎麼做的？ 這只是個大概的方案
- What did we do in episode 81 ? - It's just a rough plan.
是不是81集有什麼區別嗎？ 有！我在那集死掉了
- What difference does it make if it's episode 81 or not ? - 'Cause I died in episode 81 !
噓！那就51集，可以了吧？ 真荒唐
- Shh ! Episode 51, right ? - This is ludicrous.
你們為什麼要聽他的？我提醒你們
Why are you listening to this fellow ? May I remind you:
他穿的是戲服，不是制服！
He's wearing a costume, not a uniform.
他並不比這傢伙更配領導我們
He's no more equipped to lead us than this fellow.
沒有冒犯的意思
No offense.
看，他們走了
Look, they're gone.
去哪裡了？ 我不知道
- Where'd they go, back inside ? - I don't know.
沒人放哨了 好了，好了
- Nobody was watching. - All right, all right !
聽著格溫，弗來德，亞力克斯和我去拿鈹金球
Listen up. Here's the plan. Gwen, Fred, Alex and l, we'll go down and get a sphere.
弗裡曼, 你建個臨時工事，湯米，你放哨
Fleegman, you set up a perimeter, and Tommy, you're lookout.
不管見到什麼，給我們個信號 什麼樣的信號？
- You see anything at all, you give us a signal. - What kind of a signal ?
隨便 好的，我把手弄成這樣，然後嘎嘎叫！
- Any kind of signal. - Okay, I'll do my hands like this, and caw, caw !
你是嬰兒嗎？看好，這樣來
What are you, an infant ? Look, we have these.
抱歉 好了，我們走
- That-- Sorry. - All right, let's go.
[ Grunting ]
翻跟頭有幫助嗎？ 啊哈，是的
- Does rolling help ? - Uh-huh, it helps.
你的槍呢？ 它也有用，開槍！
- Where's your gun ? - It helps. - Shoot !
- 哦. -什麼？
- Oh. - What ?
永不放棄，永不妥協
[ Jason Chuckling ] Never give up, never surrender.
- 哦. -閉嘴
[ Together ] Oh, shut up.
靠，靠，嗨--！
Caw, caw, I said ! [ Yelling ]
跑！跑！
[ Screaming ] Run ! Run ! Run !
他們無處不在
- They're everywhere, they're everywhere. - Everywhere !
快跑啊，快快
- Come on, let's go. - Let's go !
快點！
- [ Yelling ] - [ Jason ] Hurry !
到處都是那玩意兒！
They're everywhere. Come on !
別回頭，別回頭
[ Jason ] Don't look back. Don't look back.
我們不會成功的
- We're not gonna make it. - [ Snarling ]
哦，上帝！
- [ Screams ] - Oh, God !
我就說，我會送命的 快！跑！跑!
- [ Guy ] I knew it, I knew it. I knew this was gonna kill me. - Hurry ! Go, go, go !
快跑啊！
[ Jason ] Come on. Push. Let's go. Go !
我知道，還要幾秒鐘
I got it, but it's gonna take a few seconds.
我知道了！我知道！
I got it, I got it !
向前跑 來不及了。進去，進去
- Go ahead. - There's no time. Get in, get in.
當然，我忘記了 你一直是扮英雄的，是嗎？
Of course, I forgot, you've got to be the hero. Haven't you ?
但願別人不會成為主角！ 哦，不，賈森耐斯密斯
Heaven forbid anybody else gets the spotlight ! Oh, no, Jason Nesmith--
哦！賈森，快啊！
- Oh ! Jason ! Jason, come on ! - [ Screeching ]
快！湯米，快點！
- Hurry ! - Tommy, go ! Go ! I mean it !
救命！不！不！賈森，求你了！ 湯米，停下太空艙，停下！
Help ! No, no, no ! Jason, please ! Tommy, stop the pod, stop it !
我停不了，這是自動駕駛的 走！別管他！
- I can't stop it. It's on autopilot. - Go ! Leave him !
不！
[ Gwen ] No !
[ Screeching ]
哦，好！
Oh, right !
當然，總是你，是嗎？
Of course, it's always about you, isn't it ?
[ Panting ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Screeching ]
[ Groaning ]
哦. 嘿！
[ Screaming ] Oh, hey ! [ Grunting ]
- [ Growling ] - [ Groaning ]
[ Chanting ] Gorignack, Gorignack.
- [ Groaning Continues ] - Gorignak, Gorignak, Gorignak, Gorignak.
賈森 能聽見我嗎？
Jason ? Jason, can you hear me ?
是，格溫，聽見了 感謝上帝，你還好嗎？
- Yeah, Gwen, you got me. - Thank God. Are you okay ?
是的，有個怪物正在我面前盯著我看呢
Yeah. As a matter of fact, I've got Gorignak staring me in the face right now.
但，我想我們能幹掉它
But you know what ? I think I can take him.
[ All Groaning ]
賈森, 我們準備用數位傳送器把你弄出來
Jason, we're gonna use the digital conveyor to get you out of there.
數位傳送器? 是的
- The digital conveyor ? - Yeah.
你要把我切成一百萬個小塊然後送過去？
You gonna have me diced into cubes and sent up there in a million pieces ?
是的 那好
- Right. - Well, you know what ?
我想我寧願試試和這怪物分個勝負
I think I'll take my chances with Gorignak.
我們現在就把你弄出來
這個是很保險的，對嗎，特博？
We're getting you out right now. It's perfectly safe, isn't it, Teb ?
試驗從沒成功過
It has never been successfully tested.
你說什麼？ 請等一等
- What did he say ? - Hold, please.
理論上是完全可行的
Theoretically, the mechanism is fully operational.
但那是根據你們的生理構造設計的， 而不是根據我們的
However, it was built to accommodate your anatomy, not ours.
但技師陳中士在這裡，他能搞定
But now that Tech Sergeant Chen is here, he can operate it.
這就是根據他在記錄片裡的動作設計而成的
It was designed watching his motions from the historical documents.
我是說，我不能
I-l-l mean, I can't. [ Stammering ]
我會指導的 賈森，我們來試試
- I-l can supervise. - Jason, we're gonna test it.
什麼？ 那豬一樣的蜥蜴怎麼辦？
- On what ? - How about that pig lizard ?
嘿，我能對付的了這個胖怪物 弗來德，請你快點
- Hey, I'm doing all right with the pig lizard. - Please, Fred. And hurry.
[ High-Pitched Squeal ]
抱歉，看大師操縱使我很興奮
I'm sorry. It's very exciting to watch the master at the controls.
操縱這傳輸器，與其說是科學不如說是藝術
The operation of the conveyor is much more-- hmm-mmm-- art than science.
向後站，賈森
Stand back, Jason.
Gorignak, Gorignak, Gorignak
Gorignak, Gorignak, Gorignak.
[ Growling ]
[ All Screaming, Groaning ]
那是什麼？ 沒什麼
- What ? What was that ? - Uh-- - Nothing.
我聽到一些聲音 沒有，一切正常
- I heard some squealing or something. - Oh, no, everything's fine.
但那怪物從裡面被翻轉過來了
But the animal is inside out.
我聽到了，被翻轉過來了？
I heard that. It turned inside out ?
[ Screaming ]
它爆炸了
And it exploded.
我是不是聽見那怪物被翻轉，而且爆炸了？
Did I just hear that the animal turned inside out and exploded ?
喂？
Hello ?
等一等
Hold, please.
嘿，夥計們，等一等
Hey, wait a minute. Guys, guys.
如果那豬一樣的蜥蜴已經死了 他們怎麼還在叫"Gorignak」
If the pig lizard is gone, why are they still yelling "Gorignak."
泰博，啟動傳送電路
Teb, hit the translation circuit.
Gorignak, Gorignak
[ Chanting Continues ] Gorignak, Gorignak. Rock.
石頭，石頭，石頭
Rock, rock, rock.
賈森
- [ Chattering ] - Jason,
我不認為他們喊的Gorignak是指那個胖蜥蜴
I don't think the pig lizard was Gorignak.
你在說什麼？
What the hell you talkin' about ?
哦，媽的
Oh, darn.
[ Sighs ]
快把我帶走！
Digitize me !
快啊，弗來德，動手啊
- Come on, Fred. - Come on, guys, digitize me !
不是我 來吧，你只要動動手就行了
- Not me. - Come on, they based it on your hand movements.
難道就是我一個人看到那怪物 被從裡向外翻轉的嗎？ 不，不，不
- Am I the only one who saw that thing inside out ? - No, no, no, no.
我不是那傢伙
I-I-I'm not the guy.
我不是技師陳中士，卡萬甚至不是我的真名
I'm not Tech Sergeant Chen. Kwan's not even my real name.
弗來德，不行啊，賈森 你必須自己殺掉那傢伙
Fred's no good, Jason. You're just gonna have to kill it.
殺掉它？真是個好主意
Kill it ? Well, I'm open to any suggestions.
打它眼睛，就像在22集裡做的
Go for the eyes, like in episode 22 !
它根本就沒有眼睛，湯米
It doesn't have any eyes, Tommy.
那就打它的嘴或者喉嚨 那地方很脆弱
Go for the mouth or throat, its vulnerable spots !
它是岩石，根本沒有脆弱的地方！
It's a rock. It doesn't have any vulnerable spots !
我知道了，那你找件武器，你四周看看
I know ! You construct a weapon. Look around you.
你能變個什麼武器來嗎？
- Can you form some sort of rudimentary lathe ? - A lathe !
別胡扯了，夥計！亞歷山大， 你是我的參謀，給點建議啊
Get off the line, Guy ! Alexander, you're my advisor. Advise me.
你必須弄清楚它到底想要什麼
Well, you're just gonna have to figure out what it wants.
它的動機是什麼？
What is its motivation ?
它是岩石怪物，根本沒有什麼動機
It's a rock monster. It doesn't have motivation.
看，那就是你的問題了，賈森 你從來就沒有真正關心過我們的飛船
See, that's your problem, Jason. You were never serious about the craft.
哦，弗來德，你聽見我嗎？
[ Screaming ] Oh ! Fred, can you hear me ?
弗來德，你在嗎？
Fred, are you there ? [ Screaming ]
在 你能做到，弗來德，全靠你了
- Kinda. - You can do it, Fred. It's up to you.
哦，不不，賈森，我會弄糟的
Oh, no, no, no. Jason, I'll just-- I'll just mess it up.
你在電視上做了4年，快動手
You did it for four years on the show. Do it now.
那僅僅是電視節目，我沒那本事
That was the show. I'm not that guy.
你從來沒忘記過台詞，從沒錯過標記
You never forgot a line. You never missed a mark.
[ Grunting ]
那不再是我了，夥計
That's not me anymore, man.
是你，弗來德，你只要再試試
It is you, Fred. You just stopped trying.
你能做到，弗來德 我打心眼裡知道，你能救我的命
You could do this, Fred. I know in my heart, you're gonna save my life.
我能嗎？ 毫無遺問！
- I am ? - No doubt about it, Fred.
弗來德
Fred !
弗來德，能聽見我嗎？
Fred, can you hear me ?
弗來德
Fred !
弗來德，我不想死在這裡啊
Fred ? I don't wanna die down here.
弗來德把我帶走啊
Digitize me, Fred !
哦，哇 哦！
- Oh, wow. - Oh !
陳中士 好！
- Tech Sergeant Chen. - Yeah !
哦！
Oh !
我看到你終於把衣服脫掉了
I see you managed to get your shirt off.
我做到了，歡迎回來，弗來德
- I did it. - Welcome back, Fred.
好的，鈹金球安裝了嗎？
All right, did we get the beryllium sphere installed ?
是的，我們又能量充足了 太好了，發動機和太空艙都好了？
- Yes, we are back to full power. - Great. Engines and pods ?
啟動所有設備 太好了！我們要起飛了
- Fully operational. - Perfect ! We'll crank this sucker up.
你可以把我們放下了 你們晚飯前就能回家了
You can drop us off, and you guys can be back to your home planet before supper.
不，先生，我們沒理由回家
Oh, no, sir, we have no reason to go back.
你有的，家庭，朋友
Sure you do. Family, friends. Come on.
只剩下我們這些人了
We are all that is left.
我不知道 先生，我已經升起指揮台了
- I didn't know that. - Sir, I have raised the command deck.
馬西薩，我們指揮台上見
Mathesar, meet us up on the command deck.
馬西薩
Mathesar.
馬西薩, 奎克 !
Mathesar, Quellek !
為什麼我們到不了他們那邊？
Why can't we reach them ?
- [ Growling ] - [ Guy Groaning ]
[ Groaning ]
感謝上帝，你們還活著
[ Mumbling ] Thank God, you're alive.
薩理斯 現在是你接受審判的時候了
Now you will face justice, Sarris.
無論怎麼看，你都該死
At every turn, you demonstrate the necessity for your extermination.
放了他
Leave him alone.
你想救他的命？
You wish to save the life of this man ?
是的
Yeah. Yes.
那告訴我，這有什麼用
Then tell me-- what does it do,
歐米茄13？
我不知道它是做什麼用的
- this Omega 13 ? - I don't know what it does.
我說過，我不知道
I said, I don't know.
是個炸彈？ 我不知道
- Is it a bomb ? - I don't know.
一個陷阱？ 我不知道！！
- A booby trap ? - I don't know !
告訴我！ 說了不知道！！
- Tell me ! - I don't know !
你以為我是個傻子？
- [ Moaning ] - Do you think I'm a fool ?
指揮官不該知道 他船上的所有螺絲和焊縫嗎？
That the commander does not know every bolt, every weld in his ship ?
給那個女的
Prepare a tear harness...
加刑
for the female.
- [ Grunting ] No ! Gwen, no ! - [ Screams ]
你這畜生，放開我!
- [ Groaning ] - You brute ! Let go of me !
我不是指揮官
[ Groaning ] I'm not the commander.
你說什麼？
What did you say ?
我說我不是指揮官
I said, I'm not the commander.
放開他們，沒理由傷害他們
Leave them alone. There's no reason to hurt them.
他們什麼都不知道 解釋一下
- They don't know anything. - Explain.
格溫，讓他們看看那記錄片
Gwen, show him the historical documents.
計算機
[ Sighing ] Computer,
播放《銀河探險》的記錄片
show the historical documents of the Galaxy Quest missions.
[ Galaxy Quest Theme Music ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Laughing ]
太好了
Wonderful.
你們造成的損壞比我大的多
You have all done far greater damage than I ever could have.
好極了！
Bravo !
好極了
[ Chuckles ] Bravo.
我將珍惜這一時刻
This is a moment I will treasure.
解釋給他聽
Explain to him...
你們到底是什麼人
who you all really are.
告訴他！
Tell him !
解釋啊！
Explain !
馬西薩
Mathesar, the--
根本就沒有他格特船長這個人
There's no such person as Captain Taggart.
我的名字是賈森耐斯密斯，我是演員
My name is Jason Nesmith. I am an actor.
我們都是演員
We're all actors.
他不明白
He doesn't understand.
必須像在給孩子解釋一樣
Explain as you would a child.
我們，我們假裝
We, uh-- We pretended.
我們說謊了
We lied.
你明白了嗎？馬西薩 ？
- [ Moaning ] - Yes ! You understand that, don't you, Mathesar ?
馬西薩, 我不是個指揮官
Mathesar, l-- I'm not a commander.
也根本沒有國際太空探險局
There's no National Space Exploration Administration.
我們連飛船也沒有
We don't have a ship.
但它確實存在
But there it is.
那飛船就那麼一點大
That ship is that big.
裡面有很多房間
But inside, I see many rooms.
你看到的是用夾板做的佈景 看起來像房間
You've seen plywood sets that look like the inside.
我們的鈹金球只是鐵絲外面裹的石膏
Our beryllium sphere is-is wire with plaster around it.
我們的
And our-- [ Chuckles ]
數位傳送器只是
our digital conveyor is...
聖誕樹上的燈
Christmas tree lights.
全是佈景，都是假的
It's a decoration. It's all fake.
就像我也是假的
Just like me.
但為什麼？
But why ?
很難解釋
It's difficult to explain.
在地球上，我們
On our planet, we--
我們為了娛樂觀眾而假扮……
we pretend to-to entertain and--
馬西薩 很抱歉
Mathesar, I am so sorry.
上帝，我真的很抱歉
God, I am so sorry.
現在你知道了
- [ Gagging ] - So now you know.
拉特上尉，接上反應堆
把能量推到超載
Lieutenant Lathe, hardwire the reactor core to overload.
我要把這飛行器炸成灰
I would like to blow this troublesome vehicle to dust.
薩理斯，我的人民怎麼辦？ 是！
- Sarris, what about my people ? - Yes !
很簡單，全部死掉，不是嗎？
Far too simple a death for them, isn't it ?
拉特，打開C層的氧氣密封門
Lathe, open an oxygen seal on level "C."
讓我們的朋友透透氣
Let the air in a bit for our friends.
狗娘養的
Son of a-- [ Groaning ]
把他們
Release them...
放到太空裡去
into space.
反應堆超過承受能力 緊急關閉，超負荷
[ Automated Voice ] Core overload. Emergency shutdown: overridden.
反應堆9分鐘之後爆炸
Core implosion estimated in nine minutes.
反應堆超過承受能力 緊急關閉，超負荷 嗨！
- Core overload. Emergency shutdown: overridden. - Hey !
大團圓結局在哪兒，賈森？
[ Alexander ] Where's the happy ending, Jason ?
永不放棄，永不妥協
Never give up, never surrender.
大概現在該是你退場的時間了 你這個魚翅膀腦袋的畸形
Maybe it's about time you just backed off, you fin-headed monstrosity.
賈森？ 你什麼？
- [ Gwen ] Jason ? - You what ?
你開始像你在17集中表演的那樣幹了
You're starting to act like you did in episode 17,
你這個愛出風頭的老東西
you scene-stealing hack.
哦，是的
Oh, right.
感覺怎麼樣,賈森？
Well, how does it feel, Jason ?
-這值得嗎？你把我們都害死了  -閉嘴
-Was it worth it ? You murdered us all ! -Shut up.
因為你，幾百人就要死了
Hundreds to die just because of you.
我叫你住嘴 你們一起到那邊去
- I told you to shut up. - Both of you, get in there.
因為你想扮演指揮官，幾百人就要死了
Hundreds to die just because you wanna play a big commander.
你瘋了，在說瘋話 我在地獄等你
- You raving lunatic. - Then I'll see you in hell, won't I ?
當心，賈森 拿住他的槍！
- [ Alexander ] Look out, Jason ! - Get his gun ! Get the gun !
拿住！
[ Guy ] Take that !
[ Screaming ]
抱歉，門有點緊，你們看見了嗎？
Sorry, I was-- Door was a little sticky. Did you see that ?
我叫人送一罐WD-40來(一種噴霧式的潤滑劑)
I'll get one of my boys up here with a can of WD-40.
你一直都留一手的 愛出風頭的老東西，謝謝
- You used to pull your punches. - Scene-stealing hack, thank you.
你這自大狂 不知道那是哪裡來的
- Raving egomaniac. - Can't think where I got that from.
夥計們
Guys.
看
Look.
他們窒息了
They're suffocating.
反應堆超過承受能力 緊急關閉，超負荷
Core overload. Emergency shutdown: overridden.
反應堆8分鐘之後爆炸
Core implosion estimated in eight minutes.
將軍，你的飛船已經準備好了
General, your transport is ready for departure !
反應堆超過承受能力 緊急關閉，超載
Core overload. Emergency shutdown: overridden.
反應堆7分鐘之後爆炸
Core implosion estimated in seven minutes.
計算機，關掉反應堆 不可能
- Computer, shut down the core. - Unable.
存儲器檢查失效 反應堆系統硬件損壞
Memory checks invalid. Core system's hardware damaged.
好吧，聽著，格溫，你和我
All right, listen up, this is what we gotta do. Gwen, you and l,
我們到反應堆去手動關掉它
we're gonna get to the core and shut it down manually.
弗來德，帶上蓋伊和拉里拉 你找到閥門
Fred, take Guy and Laliari. You find that valve.
在空氣消耗完之前，關掉閥門
Shut it off before those Thermians run out of air.
亞歷山大，你到宿舍去 他們如果不能把門打開，你幫他們
Alexander, get to the barracks. Wedge a door open, in case they can't do that.
好 等等，賈森，我做什麼？
- Okay. - Wait, Jason. What about me ? What do I do ?
你去開飛船 走吧！
You're gonna practice driving. Let's go !
開飛船？
Practice driving.
我們是要去關閉一個核反應堆？ 沒錯
- So we get to shut down a neutron reactor. - That's right.
我很不樂意承認，但，賈森，
I hate to break it to you, Jason,
我不知道怎麼關閉一個核反應堆
but I don't know how to shut down a neutron reactor,
除非你在我不知道的時候學過
and unless you took a learning annex course I don't know about,
我相信你和我一樣也不知道 怎麼關閉一個核反應堆
I'm pretty sure you don't know how to shut down a neutron reactor either.
是，我不知道 但有人知道
No, I don't, but I know someone who does.
布蘭登, 親愛的，到車庫來
- [ Knocking ] - Brandon, honey, garbage.
媽媽，我很忙
Aw, Mother, I'm quite busy.
快點，布蘭登 別讓我叫你第二遍
Come on, Brandon, don't make me ask you again.
還有10分鐘就好了，我保證
[ Sighing ] Just ten more minutes. Okay, Ma, I promise.
很好
[ Sighing ] Great.
[ Beep ]
嗨，有人嗎？
- [ Beep ] - Hello ? Anybody there ?
你好
Hello ?
你好？
找到他了，聽我說，我是賈森耐斯密斯
Got him. Listen to me. This is Jason Nesmith.
我在扮演NSEA 保護者的 指揮官昆西塔加特
I play Commander Peter Quincy Taggart, N.S.E.A. Protector.
我們上次見面是有過幾次交鋒
We accidentally traded boxes the other day when we bumped into each other.
是的，我明白了，指揮官
Oh ? Oh. Commander, I see.
好，你叫什麼，孩子
- Okay. - What's your name, son ?
布蘭登
[ Sighs ] Brandon.
布蘭登, 我記得你在那次影迷見面會上
Brandon, I remember you from the convention, right ?
問了一些關於飛船的技術問題
You asked all those little technical questions about the ship,
我對你發了火
and I was a little short with you.
是的，指揮官，我只是想……
Yes, yes, I know, Commander, and I actually wanna--
我想告訴你，我對你所說的想了很多
I just wanted to tell you that l-l thought a lot about what you said.
沒事，聽著 但我想讓你知道
- It's okay. Listen. - But I want you to know...
我不是一個白癡
that I'm not a complete brain case, okay ?
我完全理解那只是電視節目
I understand completely that it's just a TV show.
等等
- H-Hold-- Wait a minute. - [ Brandon Continues ]
等一下，那全是真的
Stop for a second. Stop. Wait. It's all real.
哦，天哪，我就知道！
Oh, my God, I knew it. I knew it ! I knew it !
我和我的船員遇到了點麻煩 需要你的幫助
The crew and I are in a lot of trouble, and we need your help.
反應堆超過承受能力 緊急關閉，超載
Core overload. Emergency shutdown: overridden.
反應堆6分鐘之後爆炸
Core implosion estimated in six minutes.
- [ Gasping ] - [ Screaming ]
先生，是你，謝天謝地
Sir, it's you. Thank Ipthar.
奎克 ?你在那兒幹什麼？
Quellek ? What are you doing up there ?
我利用這逃了出來
I avoided capture by using your Mak'tar stealth face.
大伙在哪？ 跟我來
- Where is everyone ? - Come with me.
路上解釋給你聽
I'll explain on the way.
好的，我們在C層第5通道 現在幹什麼？
All right, we're at level "C," hallway five. Now what ?
到武器庫那邊去 右邊第二個左轉，穿過走廊
Um, go to weapons storage, your second left, through the passage.
那裡通往一個多用途隧道系統 穿過飛船內部
And that leads to a system of utility corridors through the bowels of the ship.
打開了 我去找凱利
- Open. - You know, I'm gonna get Kyle.
他最瞭解多用途隧道系統
He knows the utility tunnel system better than anybody alive.
...38, 39, 40.
我們所要做的是關掉通往宿舍的閥門
All we have to do is turn off the valve to the barracks.
布蘭登 沒時間開玩笑了，凱利
- Hi, Brandon. - No time for pleasantries, Kyle.
現在是5級警報，你還有多用途系統嗎？ 曾經走過是嗎？
We have a level five emergency. You still got the utility systems walk-through, right ?
是的，我走過28區 修裡斯特去過更高層
Yeah, I've got sectors one through twenty-eight. Hollister has the upper levels.
太好了，叫大家都上網
Great. We'll get everybody on-line.
踩那個金屬踏板，指揮官 踩那個金屬踏板，指揮官
- Pedal to the metal, Commander. - Pedal to the metal, Commander.
將軍！我們收到消息
General ! I have just received word...
指揮官和他的船員
that the commander of the Protector and his command crew...
逃跑了
have escaped custody.
什麼？
What ?
找到他們 但是，反應堆就要爆炸了
- Find them ! - But sir ! My men-- The core implosion--
找到他們！
Find them !
好了，布蘭登 我看見5個通道，我們走那個？
All right, Brandon, I see five ducts in this room. Which way do we go ?
左邊第二個
Enter the passage second to your left...
向前走50米
and just continue straight for 50 meters.
通道，怎麼總是通道
Ducts ? Why is it always ducts ?
那裡會有點陡
- Ah, there will be a slight drop. - [ Screaming ]
謝謝你的提醒，布蘭登，你還好嗎？
Thanks for the heads-up, Brandon ! You okay ?
他們要死了
They're dying.
等等，我們要穿過這裡嗎？是的
- Wait a minute. We gotta go across this thing ? - Yes.
別往下看 我真想看看你看見了什麼，你看到什麼了？
- Don't look down. - What I'd give to see what you're seeing.
你說什麼啊？ 你在歐米茄13的正下方
- What are you talking about ? - You're deep in the underbelly of the Omega 13 !
哦，一定很壯觀
Oh, it must be spectacular.
我倒不覺得
It-It doesn't look like much to me.
只是幾面牆和轉著的風扇
There's just these few walls and this dumb spinning fan that we have in every single--
布蘭登，歐米茄13是幹什麼的？
Brandon, what does the Omega 13 device do ?
很多人相信他是個毀滅性極強的東西
Uh, many have believed that it is a matter collapser.
一個能在13秒鐘之內毀滅一切的東西
A bomb capable of destroying pretty much everything in about 13 seconds.
但我和其他很多人相信， 它是……
- But myself and others are convinced that what it is... - I'm gonna go. Go.
是個物質重組裝置
is a matter rearranger,
可以讓時間倒轉13秒
affecting a 13-second time jump to the past.
為什麼是13秒 13秒之內幹不了什麼大事
Why 13 seconds ? That's really not enough time to do anything of any importance.
13秒夠補償一個錯誤了 什麼？
- It'd be time to redeem a single mistake. - What ?
走走走
- [ Lasers Blasting ] - Go, go, go, go !
我們必須關掉閥門，氧氣會用完了
We-We gotta turn off that valve. Their oxygen's almost gone.
聽著，讓我進去
Listen. I'll go in.
我來吸引他們的注意力，我有槍
I'll create a distraction. I've got this. I'm okay.
我爭取拖住他們長一點時間 好讓那些外星人逃跑
I'm gonna be able to hold him back long enough for the aliens to escape.
那是自殺 我本來就是可有可無的，弗來德
- That's suicide. - I'm just a glorified extra, Fred.
不管怎麼都是死，如果非死不可， 我寧願死得像個英雄，而不是懦夫
I'm a dead man anyway. If I'm gonna die, I'd rather go out a hero than a coward.
夥計，也許你是個勇敢的傢伙 又有喜劇天才
Guy, Guy, maybe you're the plucky comic relief.
你以前這樣想過嗎？
You ever think about that ?
勇敢？ 是，但是
- Plucky ? - Oh, besides,
我也是剛剛才這個有趣的念頭的
I just had this really interesting idea.
你興奮嗎？
Are you stoned ?
把它抬起來，多給他們點時間
Gotta get her up and give them some time.
先生，也許我們一起
- [ Grunting ] - Sir, perhaps together--
來點馬克他讚美勇氣的聖歌： Larak tarath
the Mak'tar chant of strength: Larak tarath.
Larak tarath, larak tarath Larak tarath
- Larak tarath, larak tarath. - Larak tarath.
Larak tarath, larak tarath larak tarath, larack tarath
[ Together ] Larak tarath, larak tarath, larak tarath, larack tarath.
布蘭登，我們穿過去了，現在怎麼辦？
All right, Brandon, we're across. Now what ?
你們向左轉，一直穿過咀嚼者
You wanna take a left and then just straight on through the chompers.
咀嚼者？
"The chompers" ?
他媽的 我們怎麼可能穿過去？
- Well, screw that. - How are we supposed to get through this ?
修裡斯特，你還記得次序嗎？
Hollister, do you have the sequence yet ?
是的。次序是……
2－2－4－2
Okay, the sequence is...
two-two-four-two--
這是什麼？根本毫無意義
What is this thing ? I mean, it serves no useful purpose...
因為在走廊中間有一些像牙齒的一些上下移動，擠壓的東西
for there to be a bunch of chompy, crushy things in the middle of a hallway !
我們不該這麼做，根本沒有意義！ 為什麼那裡有那玩意？
We shouldn't have to do this. It makes no sense ! Why is it here ?
因為電視裡就是這樣演的 算了吧！
- 'Cause it's on the television show. - Well, forget it !
我才不去 這一集劇本寫的很差勁！
I am not doing it ! This episode was badly written !
好的，指揮官， 當第一個東西開始動的時候，你……
Okay, Commander, now, as soon as the first crusher hits you--
它已經開始了
- [ Screaming ] - It just did !
好，現在走 走！
- Okay, go now. - Go ! - [ Screaming ]
走！停！
Go ! Stop !
走！ 等一等
Go ! Wait a minute.
來呀，來呀
Come on, come on, come on.
走！走！
Go ! Go !
走！ 停！停！走！
- Go ! - Stop, stop. Go !
停！
- Stop ! - [ Screaming ]
跳！跳！
Jump, Commander, jump !
那個寫這集劇本的傢伙真該死！
Whoever wrote this episode should die !
這該很有意思
This should be interesting.
[ Beeping ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Chattering Stops ]
[ Screaming ]
生活中你總珍惜一些簡單的東西
It's the simple things in life you treasure.
太好了
That's great.
現在，我們最好
Now, we better get--
找間房間
Get a room, guys.
哇喔！
Whoa !
嘿，弗來德
Hey, Fred.
Hey, Fred, uh--
哦，那樣不對 哦!
Oh, that's not right. Oh !
先生，壓力恢復正常了
Sir, the pressure-- it's normalizing.
好的！
All right !
我們得救了
We are saved.
他救了我們
He has saved us.
塔加特指揮官拯救了我們
Commander Taggart has saved us !
[ All Cheering ]
太不公平了
It's just not fair.
好的，奎克，我們到指揮官那裡去
All right, Quellek, let's get back to the commander.
雷射
[ Laser Blast ]
我被擊中了
I'm-I'm shot.
[ Groaning ]
奎克？
- Quellek ? - [ Panting ]
不是很嚴重
That's not too bad.
我們帶你去醫務室，你會好的
We'll get you to the medical quarters, and you'll be fine.
為你們幹活真是我最大的榮幸
It has been my greatest honor to serve with you.
上帝保佑我，先生
I have been blessed, sir. I-l--
別說話，奎克
Don't speak, Quellek.
原諒我的無禮，先生
You'll forgive my impertinence, sir,
儘管我們以前從沒見過面
but even though we had never before met,
我一直把你當作我的父親
I always considered you as a father to me.
Quellek.
上帝作證
By Grabthar's hammer,
老天在上
by the sons of Warvan,
我會為你報仇的
you shall be avenged.
[ Screaming ]
...13, 14, 15, 16,17, 18, 19 !
...13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19 !
好啦，布蘭登，怎麼關掉它？ 按那個藍色的按鈕
- All right, Brandon, how do we shut this thing down ? - Okay, just push the blue button.
藍色的嗎，那個嗎？ 是的，怎麼了？
- The blue button-- is that it ? - Yeah, why ? What's wrong ?
沒什麼，我只是覺得沒這麼簡單
Nothing. I just thought it'd be more complicated than that.
反應堆大約20秒鐘後爆炸
Core implosion estimated in 20 seconds.
布蘭登 ，沒有用啊！
Brandon, it's not working. Brandon !
媽媽，指揮官那邊的情況
Mother, I cannot stress enough the severity...
真是萬分危急啊 別忘了把可回收的分開
- of the commander's predicament. - Don't forget the recyclables !
反應堆大約10秒鐘後爆炸
Core implosion estimated in ten seconds.
9，8…… 格溫，我
- Nine, eight, - Gwen, l--
7，6…… 我總是
- seven, six, - I've always--
5，4…… 賈森，哦，賈森
- five, four, - Jason, oh, Jason.
3，2，1……
three, two, one.
電視上總是數到1才停的
- It always stops at one on the show. - [ Laughing ]
你說什麼？
Um, what were you saying ?
- 先生! - 什麼？
- Sir ! - What ?
保護者號上的定時爆炸被中止了
The core detonation sequence on the Protector has been aborted.
不可能！ 不可能！
Impossible ! Impossible !
導彈瞄準保護者號
Lock a complement of implosion missiles under the Protector.
炸爛它
Tear her apart.
[ Lasers Blasting ]
他已經死了，亞歷山大 聽我說，結束了
He's finished. Alexander, listen to me. It's okay, it's okay.
下面交給賽米亞人，我們可以走了
The Thermians can handle it from here. We gotta go. Come on.
[ Screaming ]
我們需要啟動防護甲！
We need that armor back up !
現在，讓我能看到前面 等離子防護甲已準備好
- Get me a forward view right now ! - Plasma armor: engaged.
好的，湯米 看看我們是否能在雷區甩掉他們
- [ Rumbling ] - All right, Tommy, see if you can lose 'em in that mine field.
雷區？ 現在，踩那個金屬踏板
- M-Mine field ? - Pedal to the medal, right now !
踩那個金屬踏板! 好了，走！
- Pedal to the medal ! - All right, let's go !
幹得好，湯米 幹得好
Good going, Tommy. Great going.
全速向前！
Thrust ahead-- full !
進入雷區！走！
Into the field ! Go !
湯米，你能向雷區再近一點嗎？近一點？
- Tommy, can you get us closer to these mines ? - Closer ?
我試試
I could try.
將軍，他們甩掉我們了
General, I've lost them.
雷區的磁場干擾了我們的儀器
The magnetism of the mine field is disrupting our instruments.
等等 我看到了
Wait ! I see something.
是的！ 是他們！
Yes. Yes ! There they are.
跟上他們 我不能，先生
- Get back on their tail. - I can't, sir.
什麼？為什麼不能？ 因為他們正向我們衝過來
- What ? Why not ? - Because they're coming right at us.
開火！
Fire at will.
我們被打中了，賈森，要還擊嗎？
Whoo ! We're getting hammered, Jason ! Return fire ?
不！把能量都轉移到防護甲
No ! Divert all energy to the armor !
真了不起
How adorable--
the actors are going to play war with me.
薩理斯的飛船在以2馬克的速度 向我們加速衝過來 加速到4馬克
- Sarris' ship, accelerating toward us at mark 2. - Accelerate to mark 4.
我來提醒你，孩子
Let me remind you, sonny:
我是將軍
I am a general.
如果你指望我會後退
If you are counting on me to blink,
你就犯了個致命的錯誤
then you are making a deadly mistake.
薩理斯，我告訴你件事
Well, let me tell you something, Sarris.
好演員一眼就能看出誰是糟糕的演員 你在流汗
It doesn't take a great actor to recognize a bad one. You're sweating.
防護甲快不行了，賈森
Armor almost gone, Jason !
你這個傻瓜，你沒認識到 如果你的防護甲消失的話
You fool ! You failed to realize that with your armor gone,
我的飛船將把你們的船 像紙巾一樣撕成碎片
my ship will tear through yours like tissue paper.
你沒有認識到的是 我的飛船拖來了太空雷
And what you fail to realize is my ship is dragging mines.
哦，不！ 轉向，轉向！！
Oh, no ! Turn, turn !
我們成功了！
- We did it ! - [ Cheering ]
是的！是的！
Yes ! Yes !
是的！
- Yes ! [ Laughing ] - [ Cheering Continues ]
Yes ! Yes !
馬西薩 !
- [ Mumbling ] - Mathesar !
哦，上帝啊，你還活著
- Oh, my God, you're alive. - [ Groaning ]
到這兒來 這條船隻是一個這麼大的模型
- Come here. - The ship was a model as big as this.
你真會騙人
A very clever deception indeed.
[ Laughing, Cheering ]
[ Cheering ]
準備回家，是嗎，指揮官？
Set a course for home, Commander ?
可以嗎？ 哦，是的，只要輕輕一點
- Can you do that ? - Oh, yeah, just point and click.
我們要穿過黑洞，有人反對嗎？
- But we're gonna have to go through the black hole. - Any objections ?
[ All Scoffing ]
好的，把飛船準備好
All right, set her up.
怎麼了,馬西薩 ?
What's the matter, Mathesar ?
我們希望你能留下來
We were hoping you could come with us.
我們沒有指揮官
M-My people have no commander.
馬西薩, 我想你的人民
[ Sighing ] Mathesar, I think your people...
有個很棒的指揮官
have a great commander.
[ Whimpering ]
好了，湯米，帶我們穿過黑洞
All right, Tommy, take us into the black hole.
我們出來了，我們快到家了
- We're out ! - We're going home.
系統調校功能 所有系統正常，指揮官
- Systems register functional. - All systems are working, Commander.
賈森，我們穿越黑洞之前 薩理斯的船有股能量傳過來
Jason, before the black hole, there was an energy surge from Sarris' ship.
我們別擔心那些了，亞歷山大 弗來德，你在幹什麼？
Let's not worry about that right now, Alexander. Fred, what are you doing up here ?
你該呆在樓下直到…… 嘿，你會把我打個洞的
Shouldn't you be downstairs until we dec-- Hey, you can put an eye out with that thing.
弗來德？
Fred ?
[ Groaning ]
不！
[ Yelling In Slow Motion ] No !
馬西薩 !啟動歐米茄13 !
Mathesar ! Activate the Omega 13 !
我們出來了，我們快到家了
- We're out ! - We're going home !
系統調校功能
Systems register functional.
所有系統正常，指揮官
All systems are working, Commander.
賈森，我們穿越黑洞之前 薩理斯的船有股能量傳過來
Jason, before the black hole, there was an energy surge from Sarris' ship.
賈森，你在幹什麼？
[ Gwen ] Jason, what are you doing ? What are you doing ?
放開我 不是弗來德
Let go of me. Let-- It's not Fred.
那是薩理斯。聽我說 那不是弗來德，薩理斯
That's Sarris. Listen to me. I'm telling you, that's not Fred, that's Sarris.
他想殺死我們
He's gonna try to kill all of us.
[ Growling ]
永不放棄 永不妥協
Never give up, never surrender.
賈森。賈森！ 我慢不下來！
Jason. Jason ! I can't slow it down !
這船太大了，穿不過大氣層
Our ship is too big to enter the atmosphere.
我們必須分開，要不都得死
We need to separate, or we'll die.
我們必須這樣做 這是我們唯一的希望，馬西薩
We gotta do it. It's our only hope, Mathesar.
謝謝
Thank you.
全體船員到第二控制台
Crew to the secondary deck.
馬西薩 !
Mathesar !
再見，我的朋友
Good-bye, my friends.
弗來德，到指揮台去，我們要分開了
Fred, get up to command deck. We're separating.
上，泰博，上 !
On, Teb, on !
這是銀行影迷會的第三天
This is the third day of the Galaxy Con,
賈森耐斯密斯和他的船員們 在這個重大的日子裡沒有出現
and Jason Nesmith and his entire crew are no-shows here at the big event,
這使所有影迷 也就是人們稱作的探險迷們，非常失望
much to the disappointment of all these fans, knows as Questoids.
再見，我們很快就會回來的 等等，你們去哪兒？帶這麼多煙花幹嗎？
- Bye. Be back soon. - Wait a minute. Where you going with those fireworks ?
保護者號以極快的速度從黑洞中衝出來了
Well, the Protector got super accelerated coming out of the black hole,
以15馬克的速度衝進大氣層
and it nailed the atmosphere at mark 15,
這種速度，很顯然看起來很不穩定
which, you guys know, is pretty unstable obviously,
我們必須用超高頻信號傳送器 來給他們導航
so we're gonna help Laredo guide it on the vox ultra-frequency carrier...
煙花用來給他們確認方位
and use Roman candles for visual confirmation.
好的，晚飯7點開飯
A-All right, dinner's at 7:00.
他們出來了
- Well, he's outside. - Hmm.
[ Chattering ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Murmuring ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Coughing Continues ]
[ Crowd Cheering ]
拉來多上尉 的扮演者湯米韋伯
Lieutenant Laredo-- Tommy Webber !
嗨，湯米
Hi, Tommy !
漂亮的桃麗麥迪遜 的扮演者格溫迪馬科
The beautiful Tawny Madison-- Gwen DeMarco !
是的，是的
Yes ! Yes !
哇喔，影響太深刻了！
Wow, what effects !
另一個船員！來的越多，越讓人高興！
Another shipmate ! Yes, the more, the merrier !
這是船上的技師中士陳扮演者 弗來德科萬和他的朋友
The ship's Tech Sergeant Chen, Fred Kwan, and a friend.
拉扎羅斯博士…… 的扮演者亞力克斯鄧恩
Dr. Lazarus-- Alexander Dane !
給點掌聲 他是個英國人
Give a big hand. He's British !
是，先生
Yes, sir !
指揮官彼得昆西塔加特 的扮演者賈森耐斯密斯
Commander Peter Quincy Taggart-- Jason Nesmith !
幹得好啊，湯米
Great driving, Tommy.
哦，是的
Yeah ! Yes !
快快快
Quick, quick, quick. [ Yelling ]
- [ Cheering ] - [ Emcee Shouting ]
賈森耐斯密斯先生
Mr. Jason Nesmith !
來啊，向全體船員……NSEA保護者致敬！
Come on, give it up for the crew, the N.S.E.A. Protector !
啊，偉大的真愛 是的
Ah, true love ! Yes !
哇喔
Wow !
[ Screaming ]
他們都來了 站起來吧！
They're here for you folks. Give it up !
太精彩了
What a show !
太精彩了!
What a show ! Yes !
Yes ! Yes !
來啊，站起來，都站起來！
Come on, give it up ! Give it all up...
向我們最喜愛的 《銀河探險》的全體船員致敬！
for the crew of your favorite show, Galaxy Quest !
哇喔！
Wow !
來呀，來呀
Come on, come on !
出去的時候不要忘了 買《銀河探險》的T恤
Don't forget to buy Galaxy Quest T-shirts on your way out.
謝謝
Thank you.
哇喔！
Whoo !
過了18年又回來了
And now, back again after 18 years,
《銀河探險》新冒險！
the New Adventures of Galaxy Quest.
謝 謝 收 看
永不放棄，永不妥協
[ Mathesar ] Never give up, never surrender.